Guide to the Program on Non-Profit Organizations, Yale University, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Various writings and records [computer files], circa 1980-1999; Accession 2005-A-156
  - Various PONPO writings and records, Circa 1980 - 1999 (Box 1–5)
    - Grant Log, committment list, project budgets, vitae & general proposals BACKUP, 2005-A-156-0349; 1 (Box 5)
    - Foundations: General foundation & corporate relations misc corresp, props., etc., 2005-A-156-0350; 1 (Box 5)
    - Foundations: inquiries, proposals, gen. corresp. S through Z, 2005-A-156-0351; 1 (Box 5)
    - Foundations: inquiries, proposas, gen. corresp. S through Z BACKUP, 2005-A-156-0352; 1 (Box 5)
    - Foundations: inquiries, proposals, gen. corres. J through R, 2005-A-156-0353; 1 (Box 5)
    - Foundations: inquiries, proposals, gen. corresp. J through R BACKUP, 2005-A-156-0354; 1 (Box 5)
    - Foundations: inquiries, proposals, gen. corres. A through I, 2005-A-156-0355; 1 (Box 5)
    - Access list only use this now Cummings list database lisa techie, 2005-A-156-0357; 1 (Box 5)